Jhal
a very good morning friends and raw vivek
box with another set of questions asked
in question of the day in ashiyana actually
last day you can participate in the mother
after 10 minutes to the question
subscribe and want to see the question is the
question of the answer your questions you only have
two days left subscribe you must
know register yourself
because many people don't know
but still you want to right answer
quick options class and break preparation
daily launch brick and class chapter time
april sony bread without clothes to
tell me what do you do to stop your voice mail do
you press the clutch and press the cloth
or after pressing the brake you find the clutch
and press the brake and clutch together
or else you just increase the talk without
clutch now you don't
press the clutch openly so you have only two options to
tell this answer please watch Tantiya
Requesting you to can I connect with Chief
Minister Engineer Love once now school camp
in this regard in growth serum we want all of you to
phone daily and make a
10,000 ram mission to make all Indian roads
for everyone not only for 2 people
driving but for the stranger people you are you
Singh Rathour on daily basis of chili bhi all
aadat c interview ashram use rules and add
GPS switch off to major changes condition of
the Indian roads in the mid term for
and want to decrease the rate of us like road
accidents which on daily basis bahut log aur
log ki achche ho jate hai roz pe aur wahi chhiz ko humein decrease karna hain and by bringing
small changes and by bringing small
changes in our behavior we
can be most successful in this thing
you have seen that like now do na bhi
people jo fifth of being Indian
told you that we mean a get together
strongly get togethers to meet anyone  So,
we used to meet it this way
or we used to go to the market mostly,
we did not even know what rules were, what
lines were,
what waiting was, if we are after all,
we want our stuff first, but today
you can see how much
people's behavior, people's
awareness about things has changed, from maintaining a
two-meter distance in following the warm-up to getting it, the distance between them has
reduced a bit,
and if you go
to the market, Paytm Mirza, or anywhere,
why stand in a line, that too at a
distance, and wait for your don, you
can adopt this Champu behavior, we mean, no
one ever thought that this behavior could come,
such a big change in our perspective,
if we do it every day, can't we improve a little for ourselves,
okay, you have been
following the same thing for a long time,
but it's time to change now, and not just now, not just now, we will
change now, you can change now,
this is not the time to build your own road.
It is very important that we
bring a change in our behavior. Those whom we
love, who are your
last descendants, whom we want to see unsafe,
you should also understand that now a little
change in our behavior can make our daily life secure.
Everyone has already taken care of everyone. One person's
carelessness can take the lives of many people, can be the
reason for the death of many people.
So we request that if every person is
right in his own place, will act according to the past and will do
everything, then we can save many lives. I
agree that you people will say that
in a road accident, we will
get some response, of course you are not
responsible, but now you are definitely a partner in
that thing because if you are
not following the rules, then you are also a
partner. We are not for anyone else, not for the camera
screen, not for the policemen, not for anyone
else, not for our bedsheet. This
behavior change will have to be brought every day, but only then
we exist, not for the challan, not for
false pride. Road safety challenge for our lives and the lives of our loved
ones. We should
play our Everest for ourselves and our loved ones. We will
change a little.  So we can make our day safer and
secure so you can see
today our last one is this question
our issue is its name is
information possible from drive will clearly deny your drive our
mission is to make it possible so
we connect with you every day
three questions from rebellion we have been with you for so many days
today is the 15th day of exam today
we are connected together and we are
bringing this question
for all of you but we
want you to participate in it be a
part of plus two olympic note 19th
gifts for the giver and informative water
gates to in his knowledge and skills detention
facilities whatever you participate in the questions in which you tear
which you think is the correct answer
then request you to add that thing
in your Delhi practice you
bring it which is to a large extent something to
see  You will get it for yourself and you
can also explain to people that it
is very important to follow road safety rules,
if you are ignoring even small things anywhere,
like if you are travelling in a vehicle then
you should
wear a helmet properly, if you are driving in a car then wear it in the
middle and
not that if you are wearing a helmet only then
it is important
that the people who are in front of you and those who are
sitting in the back seat should also
wear a helmet, it is very important for road safety because if you are in a hurry or there is
an accident then it is
very important
because because of the belt your life can be
saved, you can avoid any major accident
because it is a right, there is a
lot of tension in the weather and
if there is a sudden storm or an accident then the
chances of falling into a trap
increase a lot, so it is gone and if you are a
vegetarian then you should take
care of your responsibility, you should avoid falling into the
middle of the road which is very important  If there is heavy traffic, do
not cross the route from there, always
cross from the crossing or
use the underpass instead of the foot overbridge. Now do
not cross through the middle and you are forced to
cross through the middle because
that feedback road is not very far
and is not on the foot overbridge, but
you should always cross the road after looking at the situation,
if a girl is coming from behind then do it after
stopping for a while and if you are crossing your own road then I
request you to please do
not stand in between others
because that behaviour
of a pedestrian confuses the
driver also, if he tries to take it out from somewhere
then he can create a problem, so you should
not do that, we should always be
aware and it is
not illegal while driving, if you are using the road,
whether you are driving a two-wheeler or
you are doing anything, then you should
always stay on the road and focus should
always be on the tractor.  Don't do such things
because the road is not a joke, being so careless every day
is not good because it can
create problems for many people
and Rab Mini, I have seen many children
now while crossing the road and
driving, they wear headphones, they use music
on the road and songs are at 34 volume,
they don't hear the sound of the phones, they don't
hear anything, so please at least do
n't do such things when you are crossing a
road or you
are turning right because your heart is not near the Chakra
that you will not be able to turn back and anything can happen to
you, so stay safe
not for yourself but for your family
members and for your children
too,
if you go out,
follow the road safety rules for their happiness and
always keep their happiness like this, you
can see this on the screen, Question 772
Stop Your Vehicle, what is the first switch to
stop your vehicle, now I will find the clutch
and brake, first
press the cloth, cloth dance class, first press the brake, then
press the block, then
press the block, prevent class  10th time we will
press modern cockroach together, press
break, tell me okay and press clean bag
without clothes, so tell us
which is your best way, how do you
stop this trick, that is the best way, so to
join us * that this is our
entire pain, this is the fire
issue, our pimples,
we do it at night, at 10:00 our
show Ladli Speaking comes in it, in that we
unmute our resolution on
daily basis, so you can add it and see,
otherwise you can check our website
and check your results there also
and the exciting thing is that
you have the chance to learn multiple times,
you
can participate in more than one question on daily basis, you can do it on daily basis,
you can join us on daily basis
and reserve your answers, so
as I told you when skin
question of the day you still have time, you have
2 hours  You can register your questions in an hour
and you can win more
exciting prizes in these free mode
questions. So after every 2 hours our
anchor will go with you and
talk to you about road safety
and will talk about interesting things and will
share these exciting questions with you.
You can participate in this with your family, friends and
your loved ones so that they can also
become a part of this entire campaign. They can
bring many changes in their driving behavior
and can also win exciting prizes
which are very nice to talk to you all. It
feels very good to connect with people, to talk to you and to talk about it. Today is the last day. I have been
connected for so many days that I hope we get a chance to connect with people in the future too. So I will
soon appoint you in front of you.
What is the way to stop your vehicle?
Press the clutch and brake first.
Press the clutch. Press the brake and the cockroach
cloth. I will tell you the facts. Dear Chetak,
press the brake and the clutch together or should I do it without
5th April, without pressing the
clutch, then register your answers and
you will see it there in front, now you
can go and register your answer here and
you will get many exciting exciting
prizes to subscribe to, that is why
register your answers as soon as possible Yuva Lekhan * Varna Kasana
thank you so much for this as a big and
difficult question, albeit with another set up
question of the two parts time stitch
every state thank you so much u